Made by Akutsu
She's rather humble
Hey yo, demon, it’s Emcee Amane!
Hear my lyrics in your soul, yo!
You’re in my posse!
If you’re confused, lemme explain! It’s time!
My collar’s a part of you like this nasty rhyme!
My thoughts are with you, baby!
I snuck a look.
Took a picture.
So now you know.
Use this for emergencies.
Begone.
Lovey-dovey Married Couple
Breezy
Who?!
Lovey-dovey Married Couple
Raise Your Value
Upgrade yourself!
Next Trends
Hi-ho
Lovey-dovey Married Couple
Whoaaaaaa
Got
the
same
idea!!
Futakotamagawa
Squeeze
Worshiped 12 Olympian gods, with (1) Zeus
as the king.
A polytheistic faith that believed gods to have human form
and emotions.
(2) Thales
held that (3) water was the basis of all things
Types of Pillars
(4) Doric
(5) Ionic
(6) Corinthian
The temple to Athena,
(7) Parthenon of Athens is a
(8) Doric temple.
A few days later
Comics
Consoles
Crane catchers
Right at the top
of the elevator